It's very common for people to be at their lowest before they have a realization.
Yeah.
Very, very common.
So I'm at my lowest.
I'm in between gigs.
And I had been a fan of the show called Hedwig and the Angry Inch.
Yes.
At my lowest after my divorce, my agent called and said that they wanted to give me the role on Broadway after.
Offer only.
Which that was good.
Because I was broken down, like spiritually, I knew just say yes.
This is something that you're going to grow from.
Just say yes.
So I said, yep.
And if I call back, don't pick up because I might try to say no.
And it was so freeing.
And it's the best work I've ever done.
You know what I mean?
The best work I've ever done.
Easily.
And it's the best work I've ever done.
I know.
And I know that I'm ready.